Have you seen something like this before? A whole latex catsuit with integrated
heels and I'm trying to get into it and see how it goes and see how it fits.
I put a lot of powder inside because I don't want to do it with latex oil
because then it would squeeze around in the shoes. I don't know when I tried
something on last time with powder so this is going to be interesting.
I'm already stuck.
I have no idea how I can do this.
Because it's quite tight inside and I need to get my feet into the shoes first without damaging anything.
I ended up cutting open the shoe because I could not get into it.
I recommend ordering it five times bigger than your actual shoe size.
And also it's pain in the a**.
I managed to get into it.
was an act. I'm glad I did not have to do it by myself so I would not have gotten
into it all alone. I don't like the feeling of powder with latex. I don't
know it's sticking everywhere. I think maybe the size isn't right. It's
supposed to be made to measure but it's just too small from the shoes to the
next circumference but let's shine it up and see how it looks
okay I managed to shine it up and with that it kind of like moved a bit more into place
So I think it actually looks kind of good. The fit is okay
Still not perfect. I'm still not 100% satisfied
But the look is okay
And the feature with the heel is kind of funny
To have it built in and to have it like
In one mold kind of looks like a cosplay actually or some weird movie costume
The catsuit is from Latex Catfish but I received it as a gift from a lovely
follower thank you for that it's been fun to try and get it on kind of like an
experiment how this would work and look and I'm fine with the look I really
the longer I see it the more I like it I think there have been worse latex catsuits
in my closet not really in my closet but I tried on worse and yeah with the zipper
built in it is very practical. By the way I said that it's from Latex Catfish and I
want to mention two things first there was a tiny hole which I had to fix where
is it actually? I can't see it from here because the neck is really tight. Plus I
found a lot of glue leftover spots where glue was sticking to the latex
and I had to use washing benzene, washing benzene? White spirit to remove it.
My personal resume I would not order a catsuit like this with the bill in shoes
because it is way too much hassle to get inside. Maybe it would be easier for the
second time but it is definitely easier if you just put on shoes afterwards.
Also if I put on shoes afterwards I can choose with shoes and choose more
comfortable shoes. These aren't the greatest. I'm so sorry. I'm just not not
100% satisfied with this thing here but I hope you had fun anyway watching me
struggle to get into this catsuit and you like the finished result I will see
you in the next video bye